ovguide.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy

OVGuide **respects your privacy** and does not save any personal information that is not submitted by the user (such as submitting a site suggestion, premium sections, or sending a page to a friend).

In the event that we do obtain your e-mail address, it will only be used for administration purposes only and will not be distributed to any third-party. 

OVGuide does distribute cookies on your personal computer, but we do not collect any personally identifiable information. The purpose of these cookies is just to keep a person signed in while browsing the website and remember things, like what you are searching for on the site so we can populate search fields without having you enter the information all over again. Some of the advertisements on OVGuide use third-party advertising companies who employ cookies to measure Advertisement effectiveness and they may collect information about user visits. If you would like to opt out of the collection and use of data, please visit the DAA's consumer [Opt-Out Page](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Although OVGuide makes a very strong effort to prevent links on our site that may contain spyware, adware, or other malicious programs, we cannot always guarantee their exclusion. 

When you click on a link, which takes you to another website, you assume all the risks in doing so, which is really not much different than the risk you take when clicking on a search engine results link on Google or Yahoo. 

If you find a link that you feel is malicious please report it to us using our contact form.

OVGuide respects your privacy and does not save any personal information that is not submitted by the user (such as submitting a site suggestion, premium sections, or sending a page to a friend). In the event that we do obtain your e-mail address, it will only be used for administration purposes only and will not be distributed to any third-party.

OVGuide does distribute cookies on your personal computer, but we do not collect any personally identifiable information. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number, or email address through these means. The purpose of these cookies is just to keep a person signed in while browsing the website and remember things, like what you are searching for on the site so we can populate search fields without having you enter the information all over again. OVGuide may use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers (“UDID”) to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system, and IP address. We may store your location anonymously in aggregate form to understand the general geographic popularity of our Services.

Some of the advertisements on OVGuide (including OVGuide mobile and OTT applications) use third-party advertising companies who employ cookies to measure Advertisement effectiveness and they may collect information about user visits, including interaction with content on these sites. If you would like to opt out of the collection and use of data, please visit the [DAA's consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Although OVGuide makes a very strong effort to prevent links on our site that may contain spyware, adware, or other malicious programs, we cannot always guarantee their exclusion. When you click on a link, which takes you to another website, you assume all the risks in doing so, which is really not much different than the risk you take when clicking on a search engine results link on Google or Yahoo. If you find a link that you feel is malicious please report it to us using our [contact form](http://www.ovguide.com/info/contact).
